Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 109
Attack!
After killing you...
Your land will be under our rule.
I will attack your country
like a black cloud.
I break your hand if you dare.
The noose will be wrapped
around your neck.
Even if the rope is around
my neck, I'm a wolf.
But, you are coyotes even
when you howl.
When I get up...
Then I will hold
you all accountable.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
The son of Osman Bey.
Shahzad Aladdin.
He desires to appear before the
presence of Sultan Aladdin...
and talk to him about an important topic.
Since when do you enter the palace
without permission, Dursun Fakı?
Did you forget to ask permission when
you moved from Konya to the border?
Take no offense at me, Aladdin Bey, but
a sultanate isn't the same as a sovereign.
And the size of our
palace is evidence of this.
I hope you are not
embarrassed by this greatness.
You can go big if you're free, Vizier.
In our palace, the enemy does
not move as he pleases.
We want to host you there.
You should get out of
our way for now.
It's important.
Guards.
Open the doors.
Give us a minute.
Osman Bey.
Look at you.
The world turns around and
this day comes.
You will be defeated by Bayındır, the
one you despised and underestimated.
Bey of the Beys.
Rule of coyotes...
it continues until the
wolves are back on their feet
Don't resist Osman, you will die.
He will live!
Don't you try to take my prey
out of my hands, Bayındır.
I protect your head
from the Sultan Mother.
The orders are certain.
- Why?
- The tribes trust Osman.
If we kill him now, they will consider
us their enemies.
We'll spread the
news of his betrayal first
Then we'll kill him!
Stop your men!
Whoever withdraws the prey from the
front of the hyenas loses his arm.
This is the last time, Bayındır.
Catch him!
Catch him alive!
Brothers! Our Bey is there!
Let's go!
We're here, my Bey!
You come as a guest and you want to be the
owner of the house, right, Mother Sultan?
No!
I will not allow you to lay eyes
on my Bey's trust.
Keep calm, Bala!
- Let me go, Malhun.
- You're making things difficult.
Didn't you hear
what she said?
- Not now.
- Now! Go away!
Bala.
Go away, Malhun.
Arrest these
shameless people!
Alps!
- Get out of front of me.
- Not now!
Now!
Bala Hatun, what are you doing?
The one standing in front of you is
the Sultan Mother.
If she's Sultan Mother....
This is the palace of Osman
Bey, and I am his wife!
We do not hand over the trust to
anyone, no matter what.
We do not hesitate to die
and kill for the sake of this.
Soldiers!
My Bey
Order me to behead them all, my Sultan.
Save your own head first.
- Bala.
- Stop.
Put down your swords.
Alps.
Mashallah.
I know the source of
Osman Bey's power now.
Bala Hatun.
If only you had heard my
words silently and sat down...
I would have been very disappointed.
What are you trying to say, Sultan Mother?
Let's say I wanted to know
who had the most courage.
I've seen what I want to see.
I'm very pleased.
Look well, Sultan Mother.
Be careful what you see is wrong.
My eyes are never wrong...
Malhun Hatun.
Please, visit me soon, Bala Hatun.
I want to know you more closely.
Osman.
You stand helpless like a
deer caught in a trap.
If the deer knows the mountain, you
become the prey, not the hunter.
You shouldn't have entered
this palace of mine.
How will you get out now?
We are here so that this place won't
become yours.
And we know how to take it.
Catch!
You know what you're going to do, come on.
Boran Alp.
It is a matter of state.
Stop so that no blood is spilled.
A body that has this soul does
not stop, Bayındır Bey.
While you have this mindset...
Your soul will not stay in
your body for long.
Surrender, Osman.
Surrender so I will let you
breathe another night.
Actually, I'm not going
to let you breathe.
Mongolian soldier.
I am the great leader Samagar!
Soldier is a word for those
under my command.
Mongolian soldier.
Soldier, come on, take his sword!
Osman Bey.
Everything that happens to
you is because of your madness.
Bayındır Bey.
This madness runs in
the blood of all of us.
Which will make me slash your throat.
I ask fo Allah's forgiveness.
Come on, take them to the dungeon.
Stop.
Those to the yard!
I have good ideas for
Osman and his Alps.
Take them, come on.
My Bey.
- My Bey.
- Come on!
These have overstepped their bounds, my Sultan.
They remain unpunished...
Who told you they would go
unpunished, Bengi Hatun?
Is it possible not to hold them
accountable for what they did?
The time will come for all this.
We no longer have
the strength to bear it.
This happens because Osman Bey is not
there. Let's go to the palace quickly!
Come on!
The merchants have received
the word, My Sultan.
Malhun Hatun should
think about it now.
What is going on, my Sultan?
They are market traders, why do
they meet?
You were saying they'd
get away with it, Bengi Hatun.
I have punished them with
the greatest punishment.
You were saying that you would
speak before the Sultan.
Tell me why you came.
We came to warn the Sultan
of a trap set for him.
Excuse me, my Sultan but...
Who can tell us about something
that we cannot see?
Are you participating in this trap and
making all this noise to prove otherwise?
Hadrat Vizier.
Weigh your words first, then speak!
Aladdin Bey, son of Osman Bey...
is telling you about it.
Look at you, Dursun Fakı.
Do you compare
yourself to the Vizierr?
Vizier...
Allow us, to hear his words.
Say, Aladdin Bey, who
set a trap for me?
It's a big trap, Hadrat Sultan...
I can only say it to you.
We cannot know who is on whose side.
There is no one I don't trust here.
Say what you're going to say.
Hadrat Sultan.
You can trust whomever
you want.
But while you're on this throne, you can't
trust even your blood ties.
You know that.
Sultan Aladdin is the nephew
of Sultan Mesut.
Sultan Mesut was always by our side.
He did everything he could
to keep the borders strong.
But this did not please
the Ilkhanid state.
For this reason, they
considered him an enemy...
and they made Sultan
Aladdin ascend the throne.
We will find Sultan Mesut
and make him ascend the throne.
How are we going to do it, father?
This task will be yours.
Everyone get out.
My Sultan
If you make me repeat myself, this
will be the end of you.
My Sultan.
Which of your moves did the leader
of the Ilkhanid state encourage you?
I got everyone out.
If you want me to listen to you, tell
me without equivocation, Aladdin.
Otherwise, I will leave the
decision to the Vizier.
As you wish, Hadrat Sultan.
They want to dethrone you.
They want to depose you and put your
uncle Mesut back on the throne.
Who?
Who are these shameless people?
I'll hold them accountable
for what they did.
I will make them regret.
Not just me.
I will make them regret what they
did to you and your daughter.
I eagerly await that day, Sultan Mother.
You're not going to
wait long, Bengi Hatun.
I will take the market from
them first and then the palace.
My Sultan.
There is no limit to your power.
You can take what you want
now and easily.
Why are you waiting?
Instead of stopping the caravans...
You can be the owner of the whole market
with one order from you.
It's not the market, Marta.
I want to hear them.
Caravans will not come.
When the market runs out
of goods, famine will begin.
Who will they accuse?
Of course, Malhun Hatun. She
is in charge of the trade.
I'll bring the caravans that Malhun
Hatun and Bala Hatun couldn't.
I am the one who will save the
people from poverty.
And then their eyes will not see
Bala and Malhun.
They will see your power.
Bengi Hatun.
I will give you the responsibility
of the market.
I am sure you will do the job perfectly.
I will do all I can to live up to your
expectations, my Sultan.
Konur Alp.
So?
Did you like my game?
You know the right thing, Sultan Mother.
Of course.
I always know what's right.
Well, you...
Do you know that you sent Osman to death?
Your devotion to Osman has brought the
end of you and Osman.
Your end will be like the
end of those before you.
I'm behind my case.
Whatever you intend to do...
It will wrap around your feet.
I will humiliate you first.
Then I will destroy you.
You will see it all in your life.
Put him in the dungeon!
Who are those who have their
sights set on my throne?
They are the ones who
dethroned Mesut.
I dethroned my uncle, he was blind.
He especially neglected you and caused
our strength to weaken.
You seem confident
and speak without measure.
Let it be as the Sultan deems fit
I asked everyone to get out, not so that I could speak comfortably, but so that you could speak comfortably.
What will I hide in
my palace?
Ilkhanid state lets you on the throne and its
ability to remove you from it when you wish.
My father, Osman Bey, who
gave me your name...
in order to become as important as you
and your ancestors, is in the palace.
Is Osman Bey in the palace?
He fights those who want to dethrone you.
We came here as soon as we
heard this information.
Your presence on the
throne is like kindness to us.
We, as your followers, hope to
maintain this status.
Osman Bey.
I heard he has a strained
relationship with my mother.
Will he come to
protect me though?
You don't need to be protected.
Everything we do is to serve you.
Where is
Osman Bey?
- Leave me.
- My Bey.
My Bey!
We'll chop off all of your heads.
All!
- My Bey!
- Leave me!
Close all exits and entrances to the palace
and don't allow anyone to approach Sultan's residence.
Don't resist, Osman!
So, you're trying to
put me in this cage.
I swear to you, I will make this
world a prison for you.
Osman Bey.
I was meant to see you in this position.
Don't touch!
Didn't you tell me to arrest these
people while they were alive?
Here, they are alive.
We'll have a little fun with them.
And we will crush them.
We will now crush Osman's heart.
Soldiers!
- Boran.
- Don't worry about us, My Bey.
We cannot be hurt!
- Come on.
- Come on, come on!
Brothers!
Attack Osman and his warriors as
you wish but don't kill them.
So as not to be held accountable for that in
front of the Mother Sultan.
No one can hold Samagar accountable.
He can't have mercy on Osman,
especially after he fell into his hands.
The Sultan Mother will do everything
she can to stop us and break us.
So, we'll fight to the end, mother.
All possibilities exist in this way.
But we'll be careful first.
- Will you let me in, Malhun Hatun?
- Come in, Cerkutay.
What's going on outside, Cerkutay?
Market traders are waiting
to enter the Court.
Go ahead.
Let everyone disclose their problems.
Beys, this is Osman Bey's court.
Get yourselves together first.
The merchants and the people
are in a deplorable state.
What are you saying? Speak clearly.
Caravans no longer come to Yenişehir and
those who come from Constantinople don't come.
And now, those who came
from Konya don't come too.
If this continues, we will
not find bread to eat.
Calm down, Beys!
We will not leave anyone hungry.
I'll take care of the caravans myself and
will provide everything you need.
Now go back to your shops and
wait for me to tell you.
Do not incite others.
Hang on, brothers!
Hang on!
Come on, brother.
Alps!
Oh, great leader Samagar, allow us
to crush Osman too
I have other plans for Osman.
We'll rip his heart out.
Soldiers!
Come on.
If you want freedom, rise
and fight, Osman.
Come and see.
Attack!
Attention, everyone!
Sultan Aladdin is coming.
Our first target will be Sultan Mesut.
But if not, say that the Mongols who hold
us are targeting Sultan Mesut.
Their minds will be confused
by the ingenuity of your words.
Thus, Sultan Aladdin will save
us from their hands.
Your command, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Allah bless you, my son.
It is possible that Osman Bey has stopped
the traitors' moves.
But he was captured by
Samagar and his soldiers.
You told me that you should not trust
anyone while you are on the throne.
I do not trust you.
But I will listen to what
Osman Bey has to say.
So, we have to move quickly, my Sultan.
The Mongols will try to kill my father so
that their games will not be exposed.
Let Samagar wait for me inside.
Stop it!
What's the matter, Osman Bey?
The matter is, my Sultan...
We should ask you
about the situation here.
But we are in this place that
contains many enemies.
We were not surprised by this sedition.
You will tell me everything in detail.
And you will be held
accountable for that, Osman Bey.
If I fully believe your intention...
Then I will forgive you as
you have forgiven now.
Thank you, Sultan.
See the wounds of Osman
Bey and his warriors.
Clean them up.
Then I want him in my presence.
Your command, my Sultan.
And...
Aladdin Bey will be with me.
Everything is going as we want, Osman Bey.
They will reveal the whereabouts of
Sultan Mesut as soon as possible.
You did well with Aladdin.
I will take care of the rest.
Okay.
We'll get what we want.
From now on...
You will do your job.
Your command, my Bey.
Alps!
You are fine, right?
We've had better days
than these, my Bey.
But we are alive, thank Allah.
It's okay to take a break to
stay alive for the case.
Come on.
Hüseyin.
Get ready quickly.
Inform Mother Sultan of what is happening.
Come on.
How are the merchants, Ayşe?
When caravans refuse to deliver new goods;
to Yenişehir, despite their promises...
The trade has fewer commodities, Malhun.
Mother.
Mother Sultan don't
even care about the people...
so that we will need her.
She doesn't
send caravans.
In case we don't secure the
resources for Yenişehir...
The people will depend on her
as well as the Beys.
We will be fine.
Aktemur.
Don't neglect the needs of the
merchants in the market.
When resources
decrease, opportunists increase.
We will not let anyone
open their eyes.
Mother Sultan, the measures
have increased a lot.
What do you intend?
We will burn this world to those who
try to scare us with famine.
Hear me well now.
We'll secretly extract the resources in the
castles and tribes and bring them to Yenişehir.
How will those resources be
enough for all the people, Malhun Hatun?
Until the issue of the caravans is resolved,
it will suffice, of course, but...
We have to hurry.
Aktemur.
Send Alps to castles and clans quickly.
How are we going to accomplish
this with all these infidels, mother?
Oh.
And the goods, Bekir Bey?
Were you able to collect
the goods in Yenişehir?
We collected the goods, even those
in our shops, Sultan Mother.
And we will buy the remaining commodities
in the possession of the merchants.
No commodity will remain in
the market for sale and purchase.
Good.
What about the resources found in
neighboring tribes and castles?
We've bought the resources from the tribes
for twice the price, Mother Sultan.
As for the resources of the castles, Olof
and his men have taken them.
Sultan Mother.
Where are we going
to put all these resources?
In the cave of our ally Olof.
What are the
conditions of the people?
How many resources
are there in the vaults?
The people have been acting hasty
from now on, Sultan Mother.
Thy will believe it if I say that the
famine will begin tomorrow.
Malhun Hatun will remain helpless.
She will remain so helpless that...
She will deliver Yenişehir to
me with her own hands.
Now, without wasting time...
bring the resources to
Olof's cave.
It's the safest place.
And you send word to Bala Hatun.
Tell her she will be our guest.
She will come.
Konya / Seljuqs Palace
We did what we had to do.
We knew their tricks
and fell into their trap.
However...
Now it's time for us
to play our game.
I knew they would try to kill us without
even saying to Sultan Aladdin.
So...
Who moves so fast?
Someone who keeps a secret.
Mongols...
They support Sultan Mesut to
remain a threat to Sultan Aladdin.
For this reason...
In the eyes of Sultan Aladdin, they're
more suspect than we are.
I created my game with my son Aladdin.
The power of the
Ilkhanid state in Konya...
We weakened it in the
eyes of Sultan Aladdin.
Samagar can't do
as he pleases.
Every throne sheds
blood from below.
We'll exploit their greed...
We'll get what we want.
With the power of the east...
We will open the
gates of the West.
Inshallah, my Bey.
Let's go now.
Let's do the last move in our game.
Come on.
I will find whoever is
behind this betrayal
And I will hang his head at the entrance
to Konya, to be an example to the world.
Everyone should know.
My Sultan, excuse me but...
I believe that...
who comes and disturbs the peace...
is guilty.
My Sultan.
Excuse me but...
Whoever finds sedition and
uproots it from its roots...
he will disturb the peace
of the owner of sedition.
Protector of all tribes around.
He who made the property
of the infidels his home.
Commander of the conquerors.
Osman Bey.
My Sultan.
May peace and respect be upon you.
The way you came has
never been so kind.
Either you prevented
sedition from occurring...
Or you wanted to cause mess.
We'll know the truth from
what we will hear from you now.
Thank you for listening me.
Hadrat Sultan.
For years...
The Kayı tribe and Konya have been
united.
It was like this during the reign
of your uncle, Sultan Mesut.
Inshallah, it will be so now.
Will you achieve unity with
these words, Osman Bey?
By repeating the name of the old sultan in front of the new sultan?
Your tongue has no limit.
And its consequences can be severe.
Unlimited tongues speak the truth.
You said you wanted to
hear the truth from me.
But it is clear that...
Some of the sycophants you have...
They comfort you with
lies that you admire.
Even the throne you sit on...
is strong enough to be unshakable in
the name of a deposed Sultan.
it is obvious that...
Some would like it to be.
Samagar.
Didn't Ghazan Khan send
his son to be your guard?
So that...
Sultan Mesut of the ruling dynasty...
didn't they threaten him to
ascend the throne?
Sultan.
I am the shadow of Ghazan Khan.
Representative of
the Ilkhanid state.
But if you will judge me with the
words of a Bey of the tribe...
All Konya will pay for this.
Disrespectful!
How dare you talk like that?
We are the ones who put
you on that throne.
If you speak again, I will cut out your
tongue and send it to Ghazan Khan.
Soldier.
If you didn't have a move to hide...
You would have brought us
and handed us over to the Sultan.
If our heads were to be cut off...
then it would be cut off.
But you hid
your move.
Even when you were hiding...
you threw the Seljuqs
banner on the ground.
Put the leader in the
dungeon.
I will interrogate him in private.
Osman.
As long as the Mongols
are in the palace...
Our enemies will not end, Sultan.
Even the devil acts cautious.
Bayındır Bey.
What do you think
about this?
I'm asking you, Bayındır Bey.
My Sultan.
You are known for your
devotion to the Sultan Mother.
Why did you come here?
Will you stop Osman Bey
to take the throne from me?
Or will you help me?
They've kidnapped Alçiçek.
Alçiçek and Aktemur's wedding is
taking place tomorrow.
Bayındır Bey.
This is your share of the spoils we took
from the conquest of Marmaracık.
This sword is a gift from me to you.
May Allah bless you
May Allah bless you, my Bey.
My Sultan.
Mother Sultan has defeated
Osman Bey several times.
Osman Bey is a keen and ambitious man.
I can't tell if he got
involved in such a case or not...
but...
it's known how Mongols see this matter.
Is Osman Bey wrong?
May the Mongols not
always take advantage of this?
Now...
Will you trust the
leader of the Ilkhanid state?
Or a Turkish Bey?
It's up to you, my Sultan.
I will spare your life, Osman Bey.
On one condition.
Your son Aladdin...
will be my guest
until the truth comes out.
Okay.
Okay, my Sultan.
I will not fear for my son
because I am sure of my innocence.
However you want.
Come with Aladdin Bey.
Beys can go away if
there is nothing else to say.
My Sultan.
Speak up, Saveli.
Osman Bey even interfered in the matter
of the throne in Constantinople.
Weakening the states around
was one of his plans.
We should not trust him.
Vizier.
I have no doubt.
You don't see the main issue.
The case is not Osman...
or Samagar.
The issue is my Uncle Mesut.
Yenişehir
The Tribes are out of
supplies, Malhun Hatun.
Resources have been looted in and
around the castles by Olof's men.
Not even one place left to buy
supplies, Malhun Hatun.
They are taking precautions.
What did they do with
those supplies, Kumral Abdul?
They took them away.
No one knows where.
What they could not
do with the sword...
They want to do it by trading.
If we don't find those supplies, it's
going to be bad for us, mother.
They will terrorize the people with famine
and turn them against us.
We will open Yenişehir's warehouse.
Aktemur.
Give people who are in difficult condition
the foods in the warehouse.
We'll take care of every need, house
by house Malhun Hatun, but...
There are not many
supplies in the warehouse.
Where are they taking
all those supplies?
It must be a place on the
way of castles and tribes.
They know we'll raid and take them
if we know where they are.
It must be a deserted place.
Especially the caves.
There are dozens of caves near the castles
of Karacahisar, Kulucahisar and Bilecik.
This place is such a place that...
the units can recognize
in the event of a raid.
The caves of Taşkaya, Beytepe and Yaslıtaş
are on the way to these castles.
And it's close to Köprühisar
at the same time.
Your order has come
to Konya, my Sultan.
Bala Hatun, welcome.
You said it's
an important subject, Sultan Mother.
Here I am.
No matter how inappropriate
events we have experienced...
They are all left behind.
You invited me to your
table, now it's my turn.
Sit at my table first.
Do not worry.
We know how to respect food and
how to act as a guest.
No problem.
Bala Hatun.
First, I want you to know that I
appreciate you very much.
I heard about the role of The Sisters
in the conquests. This is your skill.
Thank you, Sultan Mother.
Right, our female warriors
are very skilled.
They do not give safety to the
unbelievers or the heathens.
Mashallah.
But I think you missed something while
you were running from war to war.
The palace.
You must never withdraw your hand
from the works of palace, Bala Hatun.
Otherwise, no one will know its limit.
Pay no attention to these
things, Sultan Mother.
We don't have throne case.
My Osman Bey commands...
and we do what should be done.
Everyone knows their mission.
I can't quite believe this after
what I've witnessed, Bala Hatun.
What do you mean, Sultan Mother?
What annoyed me more than your
dagger pointing at me in the palace is...
Malhun Hatun's attempt to stop you.
It is clear that she
sees herself above you.
When one of us is fire, the
other becomes water.
So that we don't act in anger and harm us.
You must be thinking very carefully.
This is why you are wrong.
I am more sure the more I get to know you.
Aladdin Bey will become a very good Bey.
Don't look at me like that, Bala Hatun.
You also know that the young are
seated on the throne in Kayı tradition.
And adults open the way for them.
Orhan Bey will be a great
support for his brother on this path.
But I don't think Malhun Hatun
can handle that.
She may get in your way.
The mother should stand behind her son.
I am Mother Sultan today
because I stood behind my son.
People like you and I have
no other choice.
Because of your preoccupation
with these matters in the palace...
You could not see the
truth in our eyes, Sultan Mother.
Whether Orhan sits on
the throne or Aladdin...
They are both my sons.
When the throne and position
interfere in the matter...
There is no brotherhood or kinship left.
You know this.
As a mother, never forget what
I am going to say now.
Stand behind your son.
Don't leave him alone on this
bloody and dark path.
Neither Malhun Hatun nor me
differentiate between the children.
If the topic is related to the state
or if it is related to the case...
Our eyes don't see the throne.
Thank you.
Is that why....
Malhun Hatun was saddened by the gifts
the Sultan had sent to Aladdin.
If you had seen Malhun Hatun's face whe
I told Aladdin that Beyhood was worthy of him...
You wouldn't have
spoken like that now, Bala Hatun.
It's clear that Malhun Hatun has
her sights set on the throne...
as she's the daughter of Bey
and Orhan being the eldest son.
Consider me bad too.
I only think of you.
- What is this for?
- This is for my son.
Sultan Aladdin's ring.
His gift to Aladdin
Bey, who will be a Bey.
As his mother, I would
like you to take it.
Marmaracık Castle
Thank you.
We didn't find who locked the door.
I told you.
Bala Hatun must have locked him up
before she got out
We will find him,
but what about Mother Sultan?
Mother Sultan is more of a demon than
we could have imagined, Oktem Bey.
She looks like she wants to
get close to Bala.
But the punishment for their insolence
will be heavier than imprisonment.
Tell me already!
Yenişehir Market, Oktem Bey.
Yes?
It will be ours.
When Mother Sultan takes control of Yenişehir,
the market will be under our rule.
What does she want in return?
It is enough for us to be
by her side and stand with her.
We will not stand by Osman who humiliated
our daughter and us.
Do not even remind me, Hatun.
I control myself so that
my anger does not take over my mind.
Otherwise, I know what I'd do to him.
You tell me not to remind but...
I will never forget what they did
to my daughter, Oktem Bey.
You shouldn't either.
Always remember this,
so don't forget whom you should support.
The people who backdoor us
will obey us...
...after we start ruling the market.
The command of Mother Sultan is clear.
I thought she would hold a court,
even if it was just a formality, but...
...praise be upon her.
She never leaves it up to chance.
The people love Osman,
they would try to stop her.
This is clear, this is clear.
She found a way to trick people.
Huseyin.
She says "kill Osman".
Are we going to do it, my Bey?
The command is clear, Huseyin.
- You're right, my Bey.
- I'm absolutely right.
We obey commands.
We love gold.
We will implement everything
that Mother Sultan says.
Which means gold and wealth.
Right now...
Find me 10 men, no,
that's not enough, find me 20 men...
...among Mother Sultan's men.
It is time to get rid of this.
- As you command, my Bey.
- Go on.
You sleep in the bed you make, Osman.
We directed Sultan where we want.
However...
- Will Mesut make a move?
- He will.
The Sultan is young.
But he is clever.
I am sure I have made myself
crystal clear against him.
Maybe he didn't believe,
but we placed the doubt in his mind.
Whether it is us or the Ilkhanians,
it makes no difference.
He will have to order
the death of Sultan Mesut.
This will lead us to the Sultan.
And we will find the Sultan before them.
If we have Sultan Mesut on the throne...
Then Konya will provide everything
necessary for all the conquests.
Inshallah my Bey.
Inshallah, Inshallah.
My uncle.
He used to tell me all the time.
Everything is for the state.
A bloodless throne
is not a throne.
- Salevi!
- My Sultan.
My Uncle Mesut will be
executed by strangulation.
- Hadrat Sultan!
- It doesn't matter who does it.
Mesut will constantly threaten
my authority as long as he lives.
If not today, then tomorrow.
They will use him as long as he is alive.
Hadrat Sultan...
If you speak another word,
I'll consider you a traitor!
I will separate your head from your body
and hang at the gates of Konya, Vizier
As you command, Hadrat Sultan Aladdin.
Gather a unit of loyal Mongol soldiers.
Pick the ones whose tongues will be
cut off, whose eyes will be gouged out...
...after this is over.
You are going to the palace in Karakoy.
Tell me, are the preparations done?
- We have prepared, my Bey.
- Eyvallah (okay)
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in Boran!
They are keeping
Sultan Mesut in Karakoy palace, my Bey.
Nice.
The news has arrived.
We know where Sultan Mesut is now.
...we'll save him for our victory.
However, we have to stay on alert
once we get there.
Keep this in mind.
- Let's go.
- My Bey!
What about Aladdin?
You will save Aladdin.
How, my Bey?
Don't worry, you won't be alone
in the palace.
Turahan is in disguise of a soldier.
He is with Aladdin.
Also, Samil will scout for you.
As you command, my Bey.
Eyvallah (thank you)
Let's go.
Apparently, we will not fight
with the pens today, but with the swords.
Osman Bey!
Where is Osman Bey, Dursun Fakih?
And what does he have to do with you,
Bayindir Bey?
Nothing.
I was going to talk to him a little bit.
No problem, I'll talk later.
But I will definitely talk to him.
Damned woman!
She had no one to pick on,
so she found me!
I always say this.
The evil always find me!
Enough already!
She believes that she can trample
everyone who stands in front of her...
...because she has become a sultan.
Don't cry anymore, you wasted yourself.
Cerkutay.
When the time comes...
We'll make that Hatun pay.
Oh look at that!
He didn't see the onion.
He thinks I am crying because of her.
Cerkutay, what a soft heart you have!
Let's play.
Right, Cerkutay?
We'll make her pay, right?
Of course we will!
Don't be upset.
I am not crying.
Let that woman cry!
Once Osman Bey comes, she will regret
everything she has done.
So...
Why are you crying so hard then?
Nothing, I'm not crying about anything.
Watever, why are you standing?
There is food if you are hungry.
I won't care about what you eat and
drink anymore, feel free.
She cries because she loves me.
No, no I can't let her cry.
I must do something.
Ulgen...
Sister.
Now, I'm Cerkutay.
I see Ulgen as a sister...
...I mean, this situation...
Cerkut...
What did you say?
I didn't hear, what did you say?
- What did you say?
- I...
What did I say?
- I wanted to say that.
- Huh?
Ulgen Hatun.
- Hatun?
- Hatun.
What about joining The Sisters(baciyans),
Ulgen Hatun?
Get out, get out of here, Cerkutay Alp!
I said get out!
Get out, or we're
going to have an accident.
Calm down.
The thing in your hand...
drop it slowly...
- Drop it.
- I told you to get out!
We'll have an accident now!
Get out at once!
Think about The Sisters (baciyans)
He is still talking about baciyans!
Get out!
Sister huh?
Sister!
You're done, Cerkutay!
I'll end you!
No, you are playing with me!
No, I won't let him do that to me!
I, Ulgen, won't love you anymore!
Sometimes I say this is all a nightmare.
I'll wake up and this will end.
Aktemur will be the Aktmemur I know.
Don't think about him anymore, Alcicek.
Isn't it Aktemur who put you in this situation?
Maybe you didn't know him at all.
He was always like this,
he had a bad heart
No, Esma, you don't know.
It's not just me.
He does not do evil to anyone on purpose,
he cannot do that.
...but I broke him so much, I broke him
so much.
Foolish, my foolish daughter
still accuses herself!
He can't believe my love anymore,
he's doing what he's doing because of this.
Your love has blinded you, sister.
Would a man who is in love with you
do that to you?
Don't cry anymore, Alcicek.
I wish my hands had been broken so
I hadn't locked Bengi Hatun in that room!
Esma, what did you say?
What did you say?
- Mother, what are you doing?
- Let go of me!
Mother we were just talking...
Don't stand up for your partner,
Alcicek, don't!
Forgive me, Bengi Hatun!
If I had known this would happen
I would not have done it.
I don't want you neither in my tribe
nor in my castle. Get out!
The first thing you do tomorrow
is to pack up and leave!
You shameless crud!
Go! Go!
Mother!
Don't say a word, Alcicek!
Sleep now!
Otherwise, you won't be able to
get out of this room.
Do I care about wealth?
Then why is my heart
so tight inside this castle?
My Creator, help me.
Show me a way.
My sheikh.
Welcome.
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
You brought peace.
Here, my sheik.
It's not the time to sit down, Turgut Bey.
The enemy
has surrounded us on all four sides...
This is not the time to
lean back and relax.
You too, my sheikh?! You, too?
Do you reproach yourself or us?
Question this first of all, Turgut Bey.
You cannot bear the words that
will come out of my mouth
Not at all, my sheikh,
how do you say that?
I am only saying that you always stand with
Osman Bey about our issue.
I wish you looked at it
in my persepctive too.
This is not about Osman Bey.
This is not about Turgut Bey either.
The infidels and the hypocrites unite
and prepare to make the us starve!
They are keeping our supplies.
It is time to defend the rights
of Muslims first.
It is the time to defend against
to the infidels.
Your issue comes later.
But when the time comes,
we'll talk about it, too
If you gave up on Osman, not our case,
you are fine.
Defend your case, Turgut Bey.
Do not let the infidels
take your people's supply.
Don't let them.
I will be back.
No matter what happens, I won't let anyone
steal Turkmens' supply, my sheik.
- Kutan!
- Yes my Bey.
Prepare the alps now, we will attack
the infidels in the morning.
Your command, my Bey.
- Father.
- No!
Hands off!
Son.
If even a strand of his hair is hurt...
I will demolish this palace over your head.
Keep this in your mind.
- Son.
- We made it, father.
You are the one who made it.
You did your job properly.
Don't worry, the rest is on your father.
Don't feel like a prisoner here.
Captivitiy is nothing, father.
My sole purpose is to put my neck
under the knife, like Hadrat Ismail.
May you achieve victory
in the blessed path you are walking.
Son.
You carry out your campaign, we'll taste
martyrdom if necessary.
You are a gift from Allah to me.
I will not leave you with these,
do not worry.
If something happens to you.
I will return to demolish this place
over their heads, do not worry.
May Allah protect you.
May your path be open, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah.
Eyvallah son.
Mother.
What will we do if we can't find supplies?
Dear Orhan, it is not appropriate for you
as a Bey to ask this question.
A Bey plans his moves in advance.
And if he doesn't have a plan,
he doesn't reveal it.
You are right, mother.
I made a mistake, forgive me.
Not a mistake, son.
You will learn this way,
but let this be a lesson for you
Don't, don't seem despair
in front of your people and alps.
You will always support them as a Bey.
They will see the power in you.
You will be tested with these
when you sit on the throne soon.
You'd better think about this talk
before the day comes.
I am ready, mother.
I will be ready for that day.
Malhun Hatun has set
her sights on the throne
Being the daughter of a Bey and
Orhan being the eldest son, that is clear.
You may think I am the bad here.
But I only think about you.
Welcome, Bala.
What happened?
Why did Mother Sultan call you?
Nothing, she spoke nonsense again.
Didn't she say anything important at all?
Or are you hiding from me?
What do we have to hide
from each other, Malhun?
Or do you have?
No, I don't.
So, there is nothing to tell.
What did you do?
Is there any news?
We placed scouts in the caves
We will get our supplies
back as soon as we know where they are.
They can't hide anything from us anymore.
Every secret will surely
be revealed one day.
Eyvallah.
And what about Osman Bey?
Is there news about them?
No.
But they will be victorious, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Excuse me now.
I hope nothing is bad.
Kopru Hisar.
Did my order reach the
Christian villages near Yenisehir?
Yes sir.
The people will not trade with
Yenişehir under any circumstances
What about provisions in and around castles?
You know it's very valuable to us.
Everything has been resolved.
Dan and Frody collect them in Petibi Cave.
Turks may come after them.
Hey, Olof.
If they take them, it will be over.
They can't find the cave.
And if they find him,
my soldiers will end them.
Good.
No supplies will remain around Yenişehir.
Then their people will start talking
about starvation.
And this hunger will break their unity, Olof.
Mother Sultan will take advantage of this
and destroy Osman's reputation.
It means that Mother Sultan
will make them kneel.
And we will beat them to death.
What about the castles?
Can she do the same to us
to get the castles?
No.
Mother Sultan
only wants Yenişehir and Sogut.
She is ready to hand over
castles and palaces to us.
Fill me up.
Turgut Bey.
Why did he invite us, Beys?
We'll get the answer to the question that's
gnawing inside you, Sahin Bey.
Brave Turkish tribal Beys.
Welcome.
Eyvalalh Turgut Bey.
What is it, Demirhan Bey?
Is there something bothers you
that makes you stand apart from us?
What is your intention, Turgut Bey?
You betrayed your brothers with whom
you shared your meal in the past.
Are you going to ask us
the same thing now?
I did not abandon for one moment
the cause of Islam in which I started!
This is why I called you.
You defended the castles yhat you conquered
with your souls and blood!
You risked your life.
You wanted to taste martyrdom.
We lost a lot.
We fought a lot.
But what did Mother Sultan do?
She placed Olof and his men
in those castles!
We heard that when this happened you were
at the same table with the Sultana Mother
While we stood with Osman Bey...
...you were on their side, helping them.
I didn't help them at all!
I heard what happened that day at the same
time as you, I didn't know anything earlier.
What I want to do here...
What I want to do is a counter campaign.
Say what your plan is.
No.
You don't know me.
I didn't hand over my homeland even to
Osman Bey, whom I considered my brother.
How do you think I could give it
to Olof and his dogs?
That land was watered with my
martyr brothers' blood!
That land is our children's right!
You have no idea how manly I am!
Beys!
While we quarrel among us here...
The infidels do not stop.
The infidels continue their cruelty.
And now they will take t
he supplies which were ours.
And they put them in the cave of Betibi.
It is clear that their intention is to
defeat the Turkmens through starvation.
But we will not allow them to do so!
We'll attack that cave
at the most unexpected moment!
And it will be us who will defeat
Olof and his men!
Now tell me, Beys.
Are you with me on this blessed path?
My Bey!
As you ordered, we have tracked them down.
They entered a sheltered house
on the north side, before the mosque.
Does the courtyard of the house
open to the street?
Yes, my Bey.
Take us there.
Come on, alps.
Osman will not be able to
return from Konya.
All his units will have dispersed
in his absence.
There is no force that
can keep them together.
We'll strike the final blow soon, Olof.
And when Osman dies, we will seize
his castles, lands and everything he owns.
You always talk about good things,
Kantakouzanos.
Famine will make them kill each other.
Osman's death will be the end of them.
Why don't you think of the bad?
What if Osman has Mesut on the throne...
What if he marches to us with
a large Seljuk army?
Is that possible?
It's not possible, it's not.
Osman can't get out of there alive.
If he does...
Here he will face a rebellious
people dying of starvation.
How long will this situation continue,
my brothers?
Osman Bey is not present!
And there is no news from the caravans?
Where is Osman Bey?
This can't go on like this!
What will happen to us
if they don't arrive?
That's what I am talking about?
We are left alone!
The winter has come!
What are we going to eat and drink
if those caravans don't arrive?
If we can't solve this...
..I will talk to Mother Sultan.
We will come with you too!
This cannot go on like this!
Where is Osman Bey?
What are we going to do?
Let's go all together!
Why did we come here?
Why have you brought me here
where I was kicked out?
Shut up and walk, Esma.
Bala Hatun will not let you
out in the street like that.
Come on.
- What are you doing here?
- Do not worry.
I did not come for you, Subasi.
- Alcicek.
- Bala Hatun.
Don't misunderstand me...
we didn't want to come like this, however...
There is nothing to misunderstand.
You can come whenever you want, Alcicek
Esma.
What happened to you?
Who did this to you?
My mother.
When my mother heard that the one who l
ocked the door was Esma, she went crazy
She kicked Esma out.
...she had nowhere to go and
I thought that...
...you thought well.
Esma.
This place is your home, too,
from now on. You are welcome.
No.
May Allah be pleased with you,
I won't forget this favor of yours.
Esma daughter.
Other than that, you are not the one who
made the mistake, so you shouldn't suffer.
From now on, you will be under
our care, Esma.
When both your mother and father died...
I did not differentiate between
you and my daughter, Esma.
I took care of you and your sister,
is this the return?
Forgive me, Bengi Hatun,
I did something stupid
I couldn't take it when I saw
Alcicek Hautn so sad.
You betrayed me, Esma.
You can't stay here anymore.
I'll go, I'll go but...
I have no one.
The place you are going is clear.
You will go to them, those who
caused you to get kicked out of here.
You will go to Yenişehir Palace.
You will be my eyes and ears there.
I can't do this, Bengi Hatun.
You should have thought
of that before you betrayed me.
Your sister will stay with me here,
in front of my eyes
And you will go to the palace.
- How am I going to do that, Bengi Hatun?
- You will.
You will.
If you don't want your sister to
lose her ears and eyes...
...You will do what I say.
My foolish daughter must
take you to Yenişehir.
May Allah be pleased with you, Bala Hatun,
Ayse Hatun.
I will never forget this favor of you.
Make yourself comfortable, Alcicek.
Don't worry.
Your sister is entrusted
to us, my daughter.
Also, don't blame yourself anymore.
Esma daughter, come on,
let's get you settled in your room.
Come.
Alcicek.
Do you still want to join
The Sisters (baciyan)
Bala hatun, the people have begun to
congregate in the market.
Why did the caravan stop coming?
It used to come all the time!
He says right!
Is this how you keep your promise?
Will our trade agreement expire when
Osman Bey is absent?
This is not working!
Beys!
Didn't we tell you to wait,
that we would bring the caravans?
What are you doing now?
Waiting doesn't fill our hunger,
Bala Hatun.
You are too busy with your
own issues...
...while we face starvation here!
There is no starvation, Bekir Bey!
Famine is much greater than
two missed caravans.
You don't know anything.
Whatever Osman Bey did...
Even the Christian villagers in the
neighborhood don't sell us their food.
They say the agreements are over.
He says right.
What will happen to us?
We will perish.
What shall we do?
If Malhun can't find the supplies,
things will get very messy.
Aktemur, you and alps stay on guard.
Looks like they won't keep quiet.
Kutlu! Come on.
This is not how you manage a market!
The three on the left are mine.
How can they be yours?
What are you talking about?
You carry two swords,
two of them are enough for you.
My scepter gets rusty
when it is not stained with blood.
This is not food Gurbuz Alp?
Why do you want more?
look at me.
Don't race with me, you can't win.
Why would I even race with you?
Are you my equivalent?
This is fight!
They're mine and this is over.
The field is for Gurbuz now.
Look at me, Gurbuz Alp!
When we get to the castle,
I'll tie you up and put you in a box!
You have neither food nor infidels!
Gurbuz!
Don't touch my infidel!
Come on, let's tell Malhun Hatun.
The path is clean for raiding.
Konya.
It's time to change shifts, let's go.
Break the door.
Now we know it is not a trap.
We will now pounce
like a wolf pounces on a flock
We'll take Sultan Mesut and get out.
Eyvallah my Bey.
- Inshallah my Bey.
- Let's go.
So this is the day.
I am ready for martyrdom, but...
I will not fall until I knock
most of you to the ground!
Sultan, come, come.
Come on, come on, you're fine, right?
Osman Bey, they will
consider you a traitor.
Because of this move you did.
No, I have never avoided that.
Didn't you also
make the same mistake before?
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
They can't escape, my Bey.
Kill him wherever you see him.
As you command.
Hurry up.
There is still a lot of supplies
to be unloaded.
Increase the number of guards.
I did.
And I left the guys on the road.
We have information everywhere.
Keep your eyes open though, Frody.
Olof's orders are clear.
Good.
You two, go help.
Hurry up, come on, hurry up!
Attack, Alps!
Allah is eternal!
Attack!
Protect the supplies
Have no mercy on anyone!
Do you remember me, little boy?
I remember the dog I'm going to kill!
What are we waiting for, Turgut Bey?
They set a trap,
they come from everywhere!
You're on the wrong side, Turgut.
You should be on the other side!
I stand against everyone
who stands against the Turk
You are always on the side of your benefit.
Think however you like.
Burn the provisions... We will withdraw!
I will bury you in these lands, Turgut!
I will bury you, Turgut.
- Are you alright, son?
- I'm alright, Mother.
Gorbuz, load the supplies to the carriages.
We'll go back to Yenişehir.
Eyvallah Beys.
Orhan Bey.
Cerkutay.
Thank you too, Turgut Bey.
But we didn't expect you with us,
rather we were expecting you against us.
I just saved your life.
Is this the first thing you say to me,
Malhun Hatun.
There is nothing you have saved,
Turgut Bey.
We have spoiled the game of the cruels
with our ability.
Eyvallah.
You should know that
you'll see me more often.
From now on, I will face those who raise
their swords to innocents in these lands.
Come on, let's go, Beys.
You turned your back on the
first obstacle, Turgut Bey.
You should know that the void you are
trying to fill is bigger than you
If you try to betray us again, there will
be only one thing for us to do.
Never forget this.
It seems that you have become
very fond of a threatening language.
No one is unreplaceable.
And when the case is one,
a leader is always easy to find.
Come on Beys.
Close everywhere!
Come on.
- Mesut is absent, sir.
- Get out of my way!
We have seen that when
the head is cut off, the body is useless.
Yenişehir has turned upside down
in the absence of Osman Bey.
It means no one is looking after
this entrustment properly, Bala Hatun.
The market was under our control
when Osman was here, Mother Sultan.
I heard it, I heard it.
I am not talking about you.
Malhun Hatun is responsible for the market.
But the market has turned upside down.
She doesn't care,
and she's not here, to say the least.
Malhun Hatun is doing the best she can.
- This issue...
- This issue is hugee, Bala Hatun.
You have dragged your people into poverty.
But don't worry, the Seljuk state
will always be by your side.
I will put my hand on the market
as Sultan Mother.
I will never allow that.
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
Oooo...
Malhun Hatun.
You have finally brought yourself.
But if you don't allow it now,
starvation will begin.
I will work to revive this
trade that you messed up.
The decision is up to you.
Make your decision
now in front of the people.
If you give me the responsibility
of running the market
I will bring all the caravans
tomorrow with a word from me.
And if you reject me...
You will drag your people into poverty.
And the decision is up to you.
Gurbuz Alp.
May Allah please you!
Allah bless you Malhun Hatun.
May Allah bless you, Malhun Hatun.
Look carefully, Mother Sultan, see it
with your own eyes.
Both the market and Yenisehir
are under our rule.
We have no authority to give to anyone!
Thank you Malhun Hatun!
May Allah keep us under you.
Alps! Distribute supplies to the people!
- Thank Allah!
- May Allah bless you!
Konya, Seljuk Palace
- Peace be upon you
- Peace be upon you too
His Majesty the Sultan awaits
Dursun Fakih and Aladdin.
Search everywhere.
Don't go back before you find him.
Osman.
I will strangle you with this rope!
And you did this even though you knew
I have your son!
Before you...
I will strangle him with this rope!
There is something I must do
before we leave Konya, Hadrat Sultan.
I have to solve it first.
What is more important than getting
out of Konya, Osman Bey?
My Sultan...
I gave them my son as a hostage
so I could get you out.
I will get him first.
This is the most important to me.
Eyvallah Osman Bey,
Eyvallah (thank you)
Don't worry.
My Alps will take you somewhere safe.
And I will come to you after I take my son.
Osman Bey, what are we going to do?
Don't worry,
you will take back your throne.
But first you must obtain the power
to be legitimate to sit on the throne.
For this reason,
no one should know where you are
Driver, stop.
Come on, we'll continue.
Stop, where are you going?
You two go, I'll work it out.
My son, Aladdin.
We are here, my Bey!
O Right!
O Allah!
Son.
- Father.
- Son.
I would never leave you with them!
Your father never leaves you alone, son.
Thank you.
Open!
Did the Sultan
understand his mistake, Vizier?
Osman took Mesut.
If you had convinced that stupid kid then,
I wouldn't have allowed it, Vizier!
You just watched it while
I was being sent to the prison!
Ghazan Khan's anger will burn all of Konya!
Before the Khan burns Konya...
He will hold us accountable for our failure.
Now, you will go and find them, Samagar.
You will kill Mesut and Osman.
- Does Mother Sultan know anything?
- Not at all.
I sent a messenger.
She'll know soon.
Don't worry about it now.
Rather, think about
how you will kill Osman and Mesut.
I swear on the Sky God,
I will kill them both!
Famous Mongolian Commander Saveli.
We have to work this out without
Ghazan Khan finding out.
Otherwise, Konya can't survive.
He will not leave a stone upon a stone,
nor a head over a shoulder.
Untie him.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries